<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.krename.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <name>KRename</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KRename</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KRename</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KRename</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KRename</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KRename</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KRename</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KRename</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKRenamexx</name>
  <summary>A powerful batch file renamer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Un potent canviador de noms per lots</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Un potent canviador de noms per lots</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Mocný nástroj pro dávkové přejmenovávání</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">En kraftfuld batchfilomdøber</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Leistungsfähiges Programm zum Umbenennen in einer Stapelverarbeitung</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Μια ισχυρή εφαρμογή ομαδικής μετονομασίας αρχείων</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">A powerful batch file renamer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Un potente cambiador de nombres de archivos por lotes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Tiedostonimien muutos tehokkaasti eräajona</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Un outil puissant de renommage par lot de fichiers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Un potente cambiador de nome de ficheiros en lote</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Un potente strumento per rinominare massivamente i file</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een krachtige batch programma voor hernoemen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Wsadowa zmiana nazw plików</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Um sistema de mudança de nome dos ficheiros em lote</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Silný nástroj na dávkové premenovanie súborov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Zmogljiv program za paketno preimenovanje</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Kraftfullt verktyg för namnbyte i bakgrunden</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Güçlü bir toplu işlem dosyası yeniden adlandırıcı</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Потужна програма для пакетного перейменовування</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxA powerful batch file renamerxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">强大的批量文件重命名工具</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KRename is a very powerful batch file renamer which can rename a list of
      files based on a set of expressions. It can copy/move the files to
      another directory or simply rename the input files. KRename supports many
      conversion operations.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KRename és un canviador de noms per lots molt potent que pot reanomenar una llista de fitxers basada en un conjunt d'expressions. Pot copiar/moure els fitxers a un altre directori o senzillament reanomenar els fitxers d'entrada. El KRename admet moltes operacions de conversió.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KRename és un canviador de noms per lots molt potent que pot reanomenar una llista de fitxers basada en un conjunt d'expressions. Pot copiar/moure els fitxers a un altre directori o senzillament reanomenar els fitxers d'entrada. El KRename admet moltes operacions de conversió.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KRename is een erg krachtig programma om in bulk bestanden te hernoemen die een lijst met bestanden gebaseerd op een set uitdrukkingen kan hernoemen. Het kan de bestanden kopiëren/verplaatsen naar een andere map of eenvoudig de invoerbestanden hernomen. KRename ondersteunt veel conversiebewerkingen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KRename é um sistema de mudança de nomes dos ficheiros em lote, que consegue mudar o nome a uma lista de ficheiros com base num conjunto de expressões. Poderá copiar/mover os ficheiros para outra pasta ou simplesmente mudar o nome dos ficheiros de entrada. O KRename suporta muitas operações de conversão.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KRename är ett mycket kraftfullt verktyg för namnbyte i bakgrunden som kan byta namn på en lista med filer baserat på en uppsättning uttryck. Det kan kopiera eller flytta filerna till en annan katalog, eller helt enkelt byta namn på angivna filer. KRename stöder många konverteringsoperationer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KRename — дуже потужна програма для пакетного перейменовування файлів, яка може виконати перейменовування списку файлів на основі набору виразів. Програма здатна копіювати або пересувати файли до іншого каталогу або просто змінити назви вказаних файлів. У KRename передбачено підтримку багатьох дій із перетворення.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKRename is a very powerful batch file renamer which can rename a list of files based on a set of expressions. It can copy/move the files to another directory or simply rename the input files. KRename supports many conversion operations.xx</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source" width="1039" height="782">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/krename/krename.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://userbase.kde.org/KRename</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=krename</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>krename</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
